# Krisna Subarkah

Purwokerto, Central Java | Linked | 0822-4148-6969 | krisnasubarkah@gmail.com

### **SUMMARY**

Bachelor of Informatics interested in IT and UI/UX. 5 semesters experience in college projects. I always want to ensure that my work is perfect and that I can work with a team and individually. I also have good time management skills, and I used this as a computer network practicum assistant for five semesters and primary practicum data for two semesters.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Telkom Institute of Technology Purwokerto**

Purwokerto, Central Java

Informatics Engineering - Multimedia (GPA: 3.79)

*Graduation Date: June 2022* 

- Finalist in the web design competition held by Atma Jaya University Yogyakarta in 2022
- Laboratory Assistant
- Mobile Development Student

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka

Purwokerto, Central Java

March 2022 - July 2022

Mobile Development Student

- Complete the Fundamental Android course
- Learn UX Design and complete UX Case Study
- Complete the capstone project (MenFit) with a team

## **Telkom Institute of Technology Purwokerto**

Purwokerto, Central Java

October 2020 – February 2022

Assistant Laboratory Computer Network

- Assisting the supervisor in the process of implementing the practicum
- Participating in the development of practicum material
- Providing an assessment of the practitioner
- Make a final report at the end of every semester

## **Telkom Institute of Technology Purwokerto**

Purwokerto, Central Java

October 2020 - February 2021

- Assistant Laboratory Database Modeling
- Assisting the supervisor in the process of implementing the practicum
- Participating in the development of practicum material
- Providing an assessment of the practitioner
- Make a final report at the end of every semester

## **Banyumas Regency General Election Commission**

Video Editor

South Purwokerto, Jawa Tengah September 2021- October 2021

- Take videos 3 to 4 times a week for editing material.
- Editing video and audio for Instagram, Youtube, and Spotify content material 2 to 3 contents a week

### CERTIFICATE AND LICENSE

## **Certified Junior Web Developer**

**National Agency for Professional Certification** 

Publish June 2022 | Credintial ID TIK.317.02783 2022

# **SKILLS & INTERESTS**

Skills: Adobe Illustrator | Adobe Premier Pro | Adobe Photoshop | Android Development | Blender | Computer Network | Figma | Microsoft Office | Unity | Web Development

Interests: Computer Network, Design, UI/UX Design, Web Development